Now it's time for the test portion of cleaning data programmatically.
حان الآن وقت جزء الاختبار لمسح البيانات برمجيًا.
Testing can be done immediately after coding each operation,
يمكن إجراء الاختبار فورًا بعد ترميز كل عملية،
like having one definition here,
مثل وجود تعريف واحد هنا،
then converting that to code here,
ثم تحويل هذا إلى كود هنا،
then immediately testing below which would change this header to code and test.
ثم اختبارها فورًا بالأسفل مما يؤدي إلى تغيير هذا العنوان إلى كود واختبار.
But I'll separate the test portion out for this lesson.
ولكني سأفصل جزء الاختبار عن هذا الدرس.
Okay. So testing can be done visually for simple fixes like modifying the column headers,
حسنًا. لذا يمكن إجراء الاختبار بصريًا لعمل إصلاحات بسيطة مثل تعديل عناوين الأعمدة،
aka our first issue here.
وهي مشكلتنا الأولى هنا.
Slotting all non-descriptive and misspelled
تحديد كل عناوين الأعمدة غير الوصفية
column headers and replacing them with full words.
والخاطئة واستبدالها بكلمات كاملة.
So to check visually, we'll just type in df_clean and view our DataFrame.
للتحقق بصريًا، سنكتب فقط df_clean ونلاحظ DataFrame لدينا.
And we'll scroll across.
وسنمرر عرضيًا.
Okay, application procedure.
حسنًا، عمود application procedure
That used to be application P so that is good we fixed that one.
كان يسمى application P هذا جيد، لقد أصلحناه.
And about company that used to be about C. So we're all good there too.
وفيما يخص عمود company، كان اسمه C، أصلحناه أيضًا، الأمر على ما يرام.
But the other two column headers that we were trying to fix,
ولكن عناوين الأعمدة الأخرى التي كنا نحاول إصلاحها،
required qualifications and job requirements,
وهي required qualifications وjob requirements،
are hidden in the columns that Panda's collapses here.
تختفي في الأعمدة التي تطويها الباندا هنا.
This is where programmatic testing comes in handy.
في هذه الحالة يصبح الاختبار البرمجي مفيدًا.
Let's use Panda's info function to check out the columns that are hidden here.
دعونا نستخدم دالة معلومات الباندا للتحقق من الأعمدة المخفية هنا.
Info is one of the programmatic assessments we covered in the assessed videos.
دالة info هي واحدة من التقييمات البرمجية التي تناولناها في مقاطع الفيديو المقررة.
And yes, okay, job requirements,
وحسنًا، job requirements،
fixed, required qualifications, fixed.
عُدلت، وrequired qualifications عُدلت أيضًا.
Cleaning code will need to be tested programmatically just like this, in most cases.
يجب اختبار كود التنظيف جيدًا من الناحية البرمجية كهذا، في أغلب الحالات.
Let's use programmatic testing again to test that our second cleaning operation,
لنستخدم الاختبارات البرمجية مرة أخرى للتأكد من أن عملية المسح الثانية،
standardizing the ASAP start dates, actually worked.
التي توحد تواريخ بدء ASAP، قد نجحت بالفعل.
In the quiz ahead, use Panda's value counts function
في الاختبار القادم، استخدموا دالة عدد القيمة للباندا
to verify that all of these similar phrases were converted to
للتحقق من أن كل هذه العبارات المشابهة حُولت إلى
ASAP and let me know how many entries in that start date column are ASAP.
ASAP ودعوني أعرف كم عدد المدخلات في عمود تاريخ البدء التي تكون ASAP.